Guide to the New-York Historical Society Collection of Geographic Images circa 1600-2006 PR 20
New-York Historical Society
- Series I: New York City Views - Manhattan, 50413
  - Subseries IA: MANHATTAN - BOXED MATERIAL, 50554
    - Manhattan - Boxed Material - Buildings, 51854
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Rose, Roman Catholic Church of, 179044 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Stephen's Episcopal Church, 179045 (Box 56, Folder 20)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Theresa's Roman Catholic Church, 179046 (Box 56, Folder 21)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Thomas Episcopal (Fifth ave and 53rd Street), 179047 (Box 56, Folder 22)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-St. Thomas Episcopal Church (Broadway and Houston Street), 179048 (Box 56, Folder 23)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-SAJ - SZ miscellaneous, 179049 (Box 56, Folder 24)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Scotch Presbyterian Church, 179069 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Second Collegiate Reformed Church, 179070 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Second Unitarian Church, 179071 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Seventh Avenue Methodist Episcopal Church, 179072 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Seventh Prebyterian Church, 179073 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Shearith Israel - Graveyard, 179074 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-South Church (Garden Street), 179075 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-South Dutch Church (Exchange Street), 179076 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-South Reformed Dutch Church, 179077 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Spring Street Presbyterian, 179078 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-T miscellaneous, 179079 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Third Reformed Presbyterian Church, 179080 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Trinity Church, 179081 (Box 57, Folder 13-14)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Trinity Evangelical Lutheran Church, 179083 (Box 57, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Union Methodist Episcopal Church Social Center, 179084 (Box 57, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-University Place Presbyterian Church, 179085 (Box 57, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-W-Z miscellaneous, 179086 (Box 57, Folder 18)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Westminster Presbyterian Church, 179087 (Box 57, Folder 19)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-West-Park Presbyterian Church, 179088 (Box 57, Folder 20)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Willet Street Methodist Episcopal Church, 179089 (Box 57, Folder 21)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Unidentified Baptist Churches, 179090 (Box 57, Folder 22)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Unidentified Methodist Churches, 179091 (Box 57, Folder 23)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Unidentified Presbyterian Churches, 179092 (Box 57, Folder 24)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Unidentified Churches, 179093 (Box 57, Folder 25)
      - Buildings-Churches and Synagogues-Cemeteries, other, 179094 (Box 57, Folder 26)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-A-L General, 179116 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-Art Students League, 179117 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-Belvedere House, 179118 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-General Society of Mechanics and Tradesman (Mechanic's Hall), 179119 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-M-Z General, 179120 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-Masonic Hall and Masonic Temple, 179121 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-Metropolitan Club, 179122 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-National Academy of Design, 179123 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-Odd Fellows Hall, 179124 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-Players Club, 179125 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-Union Club, 179126 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Clubs, Societies & Organizations-Union League Club, 179127 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Banks-General, 179138 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Banks-Bank of New York, 179140 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Banks-Bowery Savings Bank, 179141 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Banks-Greenwich Savings Bank, 179142 (Box 58, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Banks-Morgan & Co. (Drexel, Morgan & Co.), 179143 (Box 58, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Banks-Union Dime Savings Bank, 179144 (Box 58, Folder 18)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Exchanges-General, 179150 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Exchanges-Cotton Exchange, 179151 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Exchanges-Merchants Exchanges (prior to the fire of 1835), 179152 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Exchanges-Merchants Exchanges (rebuilt after the fire of 1835), 179153 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Exchanges-Produce Exchange, 179154 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Exchanges-Stock Exchange, 179155 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Insurance-General, 179156 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Insurance-Equitable Life Building, 120 Broadway, 179157 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Insurance-New York Life Insurance Building, various locations, 179158 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Markets-General, 179159 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Markets-Gansevoort Market, 179160 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Markets-Jefferson Market, 179161 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Markets-Washington Market, 179162 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-General, 179163 (Box 60, Folder 4-6)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-Chamber of Commerce, 179166 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-Chrysler Building, 179167 (Box 61, Folder 2-3)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-Corbin Building, 192 Broadway, 179169 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-Empire State Building, 179170 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-200 Fifth Avenue, 179171 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-Flatiron Building, 179172 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-Fuller Building, 179173 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-Rockefeller Center, 179174 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-Singer Building, 179175 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-St. Paul Building, 179176 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-United Nations, 179177 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-Woolworth Building, 179178 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Office Buildings-World Trade Center, 179179 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-General, 179180 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Art Galleries and Auction Houses, 179188 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Booksellers, 179189 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Clothing and Accessory Stores, 179190 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Department Stores-General, 179191 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Department Stores- A.T. Stewart, 179192 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Department Stores- Lord & Taylor, 179193 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Drugstores and Opticians, 179194 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Dry Goods, 179195 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Florists and Nurseries, 179196 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Food, Beverage, and Tobacco shops, 179197 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Jewelers-General, 179198 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Jewelers- Tiffany and Company, various locations, 179199 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Commercial & Financial-Stores & Shops-Photographic Studios, 179200 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Government-General, 179584 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Government-Castle Garden, 1855-90: Immigrant Station, 179585 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Government-City Hall, Dutch (Stadt Huys), Pearl Street, 179586 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Government-City Hall, Wall Street (Federal Hall), 179587 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Government-City Hall, 179588 (Box 63, Folder 5-8)
      - Buildings-Government-City Hall (Margot Gayle Donation), 179592 (Box 63, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Government-Courts (General), 179593 (Box 63, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Government-Courts-Criminal Courts Building, Centre St., 179594 (Box 64, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Government-Courts-City and Municipal Courts Building, Centre and White Sts., 179595 (Box 64, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Government-Courts-Tweed Court House, 179596 (Box 64, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Government-Custom House, Wall Street, 179597 (Box 64, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Government-Custom House, Bowling Green, 179598 (Box 64, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Government-Fire Departments and Fire Houses, 179599 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Government-Government House, Bowling Green, 179600 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Government-Hall of Records, City Hall Park, 179601 (Box 64, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Government-Hall of Records, Chambers St., 179602 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Government-Municipal Building, 179603 (Box 64, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Government-Police Department and Police Precints, 179604 (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Government-Post Offices-General, 179608 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Government-Post Offices-Broadway and Park Row, 179609 (Box 65, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Government-Post Offices-Nassau St., 179610 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Government-Prisons-General, 179611 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Government-Prisons-"Newgate" State Prison, Greenwich Village (1796-1828), 179612 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Government-Prisons-"The Tombs," City Prison folder 1 of 2), 179613 (Box 65, Folder 6-7)
      - Buildings-Government-Public Bath, 179615 (Box 65, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Gymnasiums, 179145 (Box 65, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Hotels-A miscellaneous, 179627 (Box 65, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Abbey Hotel, 179628 (Box 65, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Albermarle, 179629 (Box 65, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Astor House, Broadway and Vesey St., 179630 (Box 65, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Hotels-B miscellaneous, 179631 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Hotels-C miscellaneous, 179632 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Hotels-City Hotel, 179633 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Claremont Hotel, 179634 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Clinton Hotel, 179635 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Collamore House, 179636 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Hotels-D miscellaneous, 179637 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Delmonico's (26th street, Broadway, and Fifth Avenue), 179638 (Box 66, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Delmonico's (Other locations), 179639 (Box 66, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Hotels-E miscellaneous, 179640 (Box 66, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Everett House, 179641 (Box 66, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Hotels-F miscellaneous, 179642 (Box 66, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Fifth Avenue Hotel, 179643 (Box 66, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Hotels-G miscellaneous, 179644 (Box 66, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Gilsey House, 179645 (Box 66, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Hotels-(Old) Gotham Inn, 179646 (Box 66, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Grand Hotel, 179647 (Box 66, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Grand Central Hotel, 179648 (Box 66, Folder 18)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Grand Union Hotel (interior), 179657 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Grand Union Hotel (art collection), 179658 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Hotels-H miscellaneous, 179659 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Hoffman House, 179660 (Box 67, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Holt's Hotel, 179661 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Hotels-I miscellaneous, 179662 (Box 67, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Hotels-J miscellaneous, 179663 (Box 67, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Hotels-K miscellaneous, 179664 (Box 67, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Hotels-L miscellaneous, 179665 (Box 67, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Hotels-La Farge House, 179666 (Box 67, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Hotels-M miscellaneous, 179667 (Box 67, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Madison Cottage, 179668 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Hotel Majestic, 179669 (Box 67, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Mansion House, 179670 (Box 67, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Metropolitan Hotel, 179671 (Box 67, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Murray Hill Hotel, 179675 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Hotels-N miscellaneous, 179676 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Hotels-O miscellaneous, 179677 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Hotels-P miscellaneous, 179678 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Park Avenue Hotel, 179679 (Box 68, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Plaza Hotel, 179680 (Box 68, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Hotels-R miscellaneous, 179681 (Box 68, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Rathbun's Hotel, 179682 (Box 68, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Hotels-S miscellaneous, 179683 (Box 68, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Saint James Hotel, 179684 (Box 68, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Saint Nicholas Hotel, 179685 (Box 68, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Savoy Hotel, 179686 (Box 68, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Sturtevant House, 179687 (Box 68, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Hotels-T miscellaneous, 179688 (Box 68, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Hotels-U miscellaneous, 179690 (Box 69, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Hotels-V miscellaneous, 179691 (Box 69, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Hotel Vendome, 179692 (Box 69, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Hotels-W miscellaneous, 179693 (Box 69, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Waldorf Astoria, 179694 (Box 69, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Washington (Hall) Hotel, 179698 (Box 69, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Hotels-Windsor Hotel, 179699 (Box 69, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Hotels-miscellaneous, 179700 (Box 69, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-General, 179701 (Box 69, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-African-American, 179702 (Box 69, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-Female, 179703 (Box 69, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-Orphan Asylums-Hebrew Orphan Asylum, 179704 (Box 69, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-Orphan Asylums-Leake and Watts Orphanage and School, 179705 (Box 69, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-Orphan Asylums-New York Juvenile Asylum, 179706 (Box 69, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-Orphan Asylums-New York Orphan Asylum, 179707 (Box 69, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-Orphan Asylums-Roman Catholic Orphan Asylums, 179708 (Box 69, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-Bloomingdale Insane Asylum, 179709 (Box 69, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-Five Points Mission and Five Points House of Industry, 179714 (Box 69, Folder 18)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-House of Refuge, 179729 (Box 70, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-New York Institution for the Blind, 179730 (Box 70, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Asylums, Homes, & Social Services-New York Institution of the Instruction of the Deaf, 179731 (Box 70, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-A-Z General, 179732 (Box 70, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-Dispensaries, 179733 (Box 70, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-Bellevue, 179734 (Box 70, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-Flower Hospital, 179735 (Box 70, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-Harlem Hospital, 179736 (Box 70, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-Mount Sinai Hospital, 179737 (Box 70, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-New York Hospital, 179738 (Box 70, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-Presbyterian Hospital, 179739 (Box 70, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-Roosevelt Hospital, 179740 (Box 70, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Institutions-Hospitals-St. Luke's Hospital, 179741 (Box 70, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Libraries-A-Z General, 179742 (Box 70, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Libraries-Astor Library, 179743 (Box 70, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Libraries-Colman's Literary Rooms, 179744 (Box 70, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Libraries-Lenox Library, 179745 (Box 70, Folder 17)
      - Buildings-Libraries-Mercantile Library, 179746 (Box 70, Folder 18)
      - Buildings-Libraries-New York Public Library- Research Library, Main Library (42nd st. and fifth avenue), 179747 (Box 71, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Libraries-New York Public Library-Branch libraries, 179748 (Box 71, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Libraries-New York Society Library, 179749 (Box 71, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Museums-A-Z miscellaneous, 179750 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Museums-Aquariums, 179751 (Box 71, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Museums-American Museum of Natural History, 179752 (Box 71, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Museums-Barnum's American Museum (and predecessors), 179753 (Box 71, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Museums-Cloisters, 179754 (Box 71, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Museums-Metropolitan Museum of Art, 179755 (Box 71, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Museums-Museum of the City of New York, 179756 (Box 71, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Museums-New-York Historical Society, 179757 (Box 71, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Manufacturies & Warehouses-A-Z miscellaneous, 179758 (Box 71, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Manufacturies & Warehouses-Beverage manufacturers (including distilleries and breweries), 179759 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Manufacturies & Warehouses-Coach and Carriage manufacturers, 179760 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Manufacturies & Warehouses-Ironworks, 179761 (Box 72, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Manufacturies & Warehouses-Piano manufacturers and factories-General, 179762 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Manufacturies & Warehouses-Piano manufacturers and factories-Steinway, 179763 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Manufacturies & Warehouses-Sugar refineries and manufacturers, 179764 (Box 72, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-A-G general, 179765 (Box 72, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-Columbus Monument, Columbus Circle, 179766 (Box 72, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-Dewey Arch, 179767 (Box 72, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-Grant's Tomb, 179768 (Box 72, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-H-M general, 179769 (Box 72, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-N-Z general, 179770 (Box 72, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-Sherman Monument, 180253 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-Sailors and Soldiers Monument, 180254 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-U.S.S. Maine Monument, 180255 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-Victory Arch, 1919, Madison Square, 180256 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-Washington, George (various statues), 180257 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-Washington Arch, 180258 (Box 73, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Monuments & Statuary-X, Y, Z & Miscellaneous, 180259 (Box 73, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Printing, Publishing & Newspapers-Publishers and Printers, 180260 (Box 73, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Printing, Publishing & Newspapers-General, 180261 (Box 73, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Printing, Publishing & Newspapers-New York Daily News (incl. Spanish-Amer. War Crowd dispatches), 180262 (Box 73, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Printing, Publishing & Newspapers-New York Herald, 180263 (Box 73, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Printing, Publishing & Newspapers-New York Times (early), 180264 (Box 73, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Printing, Publishing & Newspapers-New York Times, 180265 (Box 73, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Printing, Publishing & Newspapers-Pulitzer/World Building, 180266 (Box 73, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Printing, Publishing & Newspapers-Tribune Building, 180267 (Box 73, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Printing, Publishing & Newspapers-Staats Zeitung, 180268 (Box 73, Folder 16)
      - Buildings-Residences-A miscellaneous, 180269 (Box 74, Folder 1)
      - Buildings-Residences-Adams, John (See Richmond Hill), 180270
      - Buildings-Residences-Alwyn Court, 180271 (Box 74, Folder 2)
      - Buildings-Residences-Ansonia, 180272 (Box 74, Folder 3)
      - Buildings-Residences-Apthorpe Mansion, W. 91st street and Ninth Ave, 180273 (Box 74, Folder 4)
      - Buildings-Residences-Astor family residences, 180274 (Box 74, Folder 5)
      - Buildings-Residences-Audubon, John James, residence, 180275 (Box 74, Folder 6)
      - Buildings-Residences-B miscellaneous, 180276 (Box 74, Folder 7)
      - Buildings-Residences-Beekman family residences, 180277 (Box 74, Folder 8)
      - Buildings-Residences-Blumenthal, George and Florence, 180278 (Box 74, Folder 9)
      - Buildings-Residences-Bradhurst family, "Pinehurst", 180279 (Box 74, Folder 10)
      - Buildings-Residences-Brevoort Houses, 180280 (Box 74, Folder 11)
      - Buildings-Residences-Burr, Aaron (See Richmond Hill), 180281
      - Buildings-Residences-Bussing House, 180282 (Box 74, Folder 12)
      - Buildings-Residences-C miscellaneous, 180283 (Box 74, Folder 13)
      - Buildings-Residences-Clark, Cyrus, residence, Riverside Drive at 90th street, 180284 (Box 74, Folder 14)
      - Buildings-Residences-Coster House, 30th street and First Ave, 180285 (Box 74, Folder 15)
      - Buildings-Residences-Cromwell Residence, 12 W. 49th street, 180286 (Box 74, Folder 16)